Meet Professor Jason Arday, diagnosed with autism spectrum
disorder at the age of three. A man who couldn't speak
until the age of 11 and couldn't read or write until he was
18.
Hello, Jason, As she always did. And I just responded.
Hello. It's quite a strange thing to hear your own voice
for the first time when you're 11. I didn't expect my voice
to sound like this. Doctors once believed he might need
lifelong care, but he chose a different path. He turned
struggle into strength and a dream into reality. Today, he
is a professor at the University of Cambridge and one of
the youngest black professors in its history.
Now he's bringing that powerful story and Global Insight to
the African Allied Health Care Summit 2026 in Accra, Ghana
as a keynote speaker.
This is more than just the talk, it's a chance to learn
from a mind that redefined what's possible. If you're ready
to be inspired, challenged, and transformed, this is where
you need to be. Register now and be part of something
bigger.